# Prasenjit Malakar

+91-9863970863 | https://click2jit.github.io/|click2jit@qmail.com

# **EDUCATION**

#### **IGNOU**

MASTER OF COMPUTER APPLICATION Dec 2014 | Agartala, India

# TRIPURA UNIVERSITY BCA

July 2011 | Kailashahar, Tripura

# LINKS

Tryhackme://click2jit LinkedIn://click2jit Github://click2jit Twitter://click2jit

# **COURSEWORK**

#### **PENETRATION TESTING**

Information Gathering (Reconnaissance) Scanning and Enumeration Vulnerability Scanning with Nessus Exploitation Exploit Development (Buffer Overflows) Privilege Escalation Attacking Active Directory

Wireless Penetration Testing

#### **DEGREE**

OWASP top 10

Algorithms and Data Structure
Operating Systems
DBMS
Object Oriented Programming
Data Communication and Computer
Networking

# **SKILLS**

#### **TECHNICAL**

- Host and Networking Auditing
- Assessment Methodologies
- Host and Networking Penetration Testing
- Web Application Penetration Testing
- Vulnerability Assessment Network Analyzer • Linux • SQL • Metasploit
- Nmap OSINT Security Audit SIEM
- Routing and Switching Networking
- OSI Model

#### **PROGRAMMING**

Java • Python • Javascript ¡Query • C • C++ • CSS

### SUMMARY

Self-Motivated, quick learner, hard-working, enthusiastic individual seeking a position in the field of Cybersecurity as a Penetration Tester. Professional with 11+ years of experience in network design, escalation support, network and systems administration. Skilled in delivering technical customer support, managing network operations, and maintaining Organization-wide area networks.

## **EXPERIENCE**

### GA DIGITAL WEB WORD PVT. LTD. | NETWORK CUM FIELD ENGINEER

Jan 2023 - Present | DM and Collector Office, Unakoti, Tripura

- Responsible for managing lease line connectivity for District's PoPs.
- Proactively monitored network performance and coordinated restoration efforts with lease line vendors in case of disruptions.

# **WIPRO LIMITED** | SENIOR NETWORK CUM FIELD ENGINEER - ADMINISTRATOR

Feb 2018 - Dec 2022 | At National Informatics Centre, Unakoti, Tripura

- Configuration and monitoring of L2 Switches, Routers and IP phones.
- Network Traffic Monitoring using Netflow Analyzer | IP allocation and management of Govt. Offices Under State Wide Area Network (SWAN).
- Prevented unauthorized access to the network, MAC filtering

# **RENOVISION AUTOMATION SERVICES PVT. LTD.** | NETWORK CUM FIELD ENGINEER

July 2017 – Jan 2018 | At National Informatics Centre, Unakoti, Tripura

- Monitoring systems, networks and infrastructure using Nagios.
- Asset Management, Bandwidth Management, Antivirus Log Collection.

#### WIPRO INFOTECH PVT. LTD. | NETWORK - ASSOCIATE MANAGEMENT

Aug 2012 – June 2017 | At National Informatics Centre, Unakoti, Tripura

• Installation and maintenance of Network devices, Computer Systems, APs

### HCL INFOSYSTEM | NETWORK FIELD ENGINEER

Sep 2011 – June 2012 | At National Informatics Centre, Unakoti, Tripura

## **PROJECTS**

PYTHON KEYLOGGER | PYTHON, GITHUB GIST - Link

#### **DISTRICT WEBSITE OF UNAKOTI** | S3WAAS, WORDPRESS

www.unakoti.nic.in | NIC Unakoti, Tripura

Developed and maintaing Official Website of Unakoti District, Tripura.

# **REVENUE COURT CASE MONITORING SYSTEM** | JAVA , POSTGRESOL

https://rccms.tripura.gov.in/ | Govt. Of Tripura Developed modules in RCCMS for Tripura Government.

# **CERTIFICATE**

2023 INE Junior Penetration Tester (eJPT)

2023 Google Google Cybersecurity Professional Certificate